MUTSUGI.
夢繼法師。
That's so...
就是這樣...
I am the one who dwells in the forbidden fruit.
我是住在禁果裡的人。
you··.
你··。
The heart of this woman who despaired over her unrewarding mission...
這個對自己毫無回報的使命感到絕望的女人的心......
And due to her obsession with wishing for a world without Grudge...
也因為她沉迷於渴望一個沒有陰我的世界…
The Gate of Destruction have awakened.
破壞之門已經甦醒。
You guys lose.
你們輸了。
The human world will once again become a world of chaos.
人類世界將再次變成混亂的世界。
No way.
決不。
Obi, believe in your friends.
歐比，相信你的朋友。
Original work by KEITA AMEMIYA.
雨宮惠太的原創作品。
Produced by TOHOKUSHINSHA.
東北新社製作。
Executive producer KIYOTAKA NINOMIYA.
執行製片二宮清隆。
GARO：Heir To Steel Armor.
牙狼＜GARO＞鋼之繼承者。
WATARU KURIYAMA.
栗山涉。
ON NAKANO.
在中野。
MIKO NAKAZAWA.
中澤美子。
TOMOKA KUROTANI.
黑谷智香。
MASATO HAGIWARA.
萩原正人。
HIRONOBU KAGEYAMA.
影山博宣。
KENTEZ ASAKA, AKIHIRO YAMAMOTO, SHUN NISHIME.
朝坂肯特斯、山本昭宏、西目俊。
Planning/producer Tanaka Aya, producer Higa Ichiro, SHUHEI OKABAYASHI.
企劃/製作人田中文、製作人比嘉一郎、岡林修平。
Screenplay NORIKATSU KODAMA, script cooperation YASUHIRO MATSUDA.
編劇小玉則勝，劇本合作松田泰弘。
Opening theme song "GARO：Heir To Steel Armor with JAM Project", composed and arranged by YUKI KAJIURA.
片頭曲《牙狼＜GARO＞鋼之繼承者with JAM Project》由梶浦由紀作曲、編曲。
Music producer SHUNJI INOUE, music YOSHICHIKA KURIYAMA, SHIHO TERADA.
音樂製作人井上俊二、音樂人栗山吉親、寺田志保。
Photography by JUNYA HOSHI, AKIRA NISHIOKA.
攝影：JUNYA HOSHI、AKIRA NISHIOKA。
Costume design YOU-KO.
服裝設計YOU-KO。
Stunt director MASAKI SUZUMURA.
特技導演鈴村正樹。
Director: YASUHIRO MATSUDA.
導演：松田康弘。
Inherit.
繼承。
SOUMA.
創磨。
Let's join forces and fight.
讓我們攜手並肩，戰鬥吧。
let's go.
我們走吧。
Okay.
好的。
SOUMA.
創磨。
RYUGA.
流牙。
Disappear, the light of hope that illuminates the darkness.
消失，照亮黑暗的希望之光。
RYUGA, if you remain in this state, you will be consumed by evil.
流牙，如果你繼續處於這種狀態，你就會被邪惡吞噬。
RYUGA.
流牙。
Try turning darkness into light.
試著將黑暗變成光明。
SENKOUKENBU and SENEIKENBU are two sides of the same coin.
閃光劍舞和SENEIKENBU是一個問題的兩個面向。
You have overcome the trials of darkness, so you are sure to master it someday.
你已經克服了黑暗的考驗，所以有一天你一定會掌握它。
I will transform all of GARO's golden light into the power of darkness.
我會將牙狼的所有金光轉化為黑暗之力。
what?
什麼？
Return to darkness.
返回黑暗。
RYUGA.
流牙。
SOUMA.
創磨。
RYUGA slashed the HORROR.
流牙斬斷了駭魔。
RYUGA.
流牙。
You freed MUTSUGI from HORROR.
你讓夢繼法師擺脫了駭魔。
thank you.
謝謝。
We now have to do something about the Gate of Destruction.
我們現在必須對破壞之門採取一些措施。
The dragon's head held by the Gate of Destruction is a HORROR used by our ancestors to seal the gate.
破壞之門所持有的龍頭，是我們的祖先用來封印大門的駭魔。
It has awakened from a long slumber and is seeking the souls of people.
它從沉睡中甦醒，正在尋找人們的靈魂。
In that state, we can't get close to it.
在那種狀態下，我們無法接近它。
SOUMA.
創磨。
There is a way.
有一種方法。
It's a SENKOUKENBU.
這是閃光劍舞。
I've never succeeded in that trick.
我這個伎倆從來沒有成功過。
GODOU believed that you could master the SENKOUKENBU.
護道相信你能夠掌握閃光劍舞。
It is true that you were swallowed up by darkness that day.
確實，那天你被黑暗吞沒了。
However, GODOU said:
然而護道：
It was impossible for SOUMA to do that.
創磨不可能做到這一點。
No, it's the opposite.
不，恰恰相反。
He heard my voice and came back from the darkness of his own free will.
他聽到了我的聲音，並自願從黑暗中回來。
If he improves himself from now on, he will definitely be able to overcome the darkness.
如果他從現在開始提升自己，一定能夠戰勝黑暗。
After all, SOUMA is a suitable successor to ZANGO.
畢竟， 創磨是ZANGO的合適接班人。
Did my father say that?
我父親這麼說過嗎？
SOUMA.
創磨。
believe in yourself.
相信你自己。
I believe in you too.
我也相信你。
SOUMA.
創磨。
You can do that, right?
你能做到，對吧？
I'll do it.
我會做的。
RYUGA, you need to be purified before you can wear the armor.
流牙，你需要淨化之後才能穿上鎧甲。
What is that?
那是什麼？
This is the sword that Igus had.
這是伊古斯所擁有的劍。
Someday, please inherit the will of my friend GODOU.
總有一天，請繼承我的朋友護道的意志。
Igus.
伊古斯。
Let's fight together.
我們一起戰鬥吧。
Igus will also help you.
伊古斯也會為您提供協助。
Okay.
好的。
SOUMA.
創磨。
let's go.
我們走吧。
Okay.
好的。
Accept your own darkness.
接受自己的黑暗。
And turn that into light, SOUMA.
並將其轉化為光，創磨。
I accept my own darkness.
我接受自己的黑暗。
And I turn it into light.
我把它變成光。
Believe in yourself.
相信你自己。
Put your thoughts as a makai order into it.
把你當作守護者的想法放進去。
Get over it, SOUMA.
克服它吧，創磨。
now.
現在。
You did it.
你做到了。
RYUGA.
流牙。
That was a wonderful SENKOUKENBU.
那是一場精彩的閃光劍舞。
If GODOU saw us now, he would recognize our abilities.
如果護道現在看到我們，他一定會認清我們的能力。
SOUMA.
創磨。
What happened to the Gate of Destruction?
破壞之門發生了什麼事？
Our ancestors must have realized this through great sacrifice.
我們的祖先一定是透過巨大的犧牲來認識這一點的。
It is simply impossible to destroy the Gate of Destruction.
破壞之門根本不可能被摧毀。
This world has light and darkness.
這個世界有光明，也有黑暗。
Similarly, they chose to coexist with the Gate of Destruction.
同樣，他們選擇了與破壞之門共存。
RYUGA.
流牙。
I think I understand what you said.
我想我明白你所說的。
Until now, I had thought that as long as I lived, all I had to do was kill HORROR.
直到現在，我都以為只要我活著，我要做的就是消滅駭魔。
But I was wrong.
但我錯了。
That's right.
這是正確的。
That alone will not lead to the future.
僅此一點並不能通往未來。
This is what we can do.
這是我們能做的。
As makai order, we must pass on the heart of HAGANE to future generations.
身為守護者，我們必須將①鋼鎧之心傳承給子孫後代。
That's right, RYUGA.
沒錯，流牙。
Are you leaving now?
你現在走嗎？
yes.
是的。
I have to purify GARO's armor as soon as possible.
我得盡快淨化牙狼的鎧甲。
Besides, there are a splendid Makai Priests and three swordsmen here.
此外，這裡還有一位出色的魔戒法師和三位劍士。
We will pass it on to the future.
我們將把它傳遞給未來。
My father and their thoughts.
我的父親和他們的想法。
because··.
因為··。
Because we are all heirs of HAGANE.
因為我們都是①鋼鎧的繼承人。
GARO：Heir To Steel Armor .
牙狼＜GARO＞鋼之繼承者。
WATARU KURIYAMA as RYUGA DOUGAI .
流牙山涉飾演道外。
HIRONOBU KAGEYAMA as ZARUBA.
影山博宣飾演 ZARUBA。
ON NAKANO as SHIRAHANE SOUMA.
ON NAKANO創磨白羽相馬。
MIKO NAKAZAWA as KOYORI.
中澤美子飾演來依。
TOMOKA KUROTANI plays MUTSUGI.
黑谷智華飾演夢繼法師。
SARA OSHINO plays the role of seducer.
忍野薩拉飾演誘惑者。
KENTEZ ASAKA as Igus.
KENTEZ ASAKA 飾伊古斯。
AKIHIRO YAMAMOTO as Ron.
山本昭宏飾演龍。
SHUN NISHIME as Obi.
西舜飾演歐比。
MASATO HAGIWARA as SHIRAHANE GODOU.
萩原正人飾演白羽護道。
YUKA SUZUMURA ​​as IRUVA.
鈴村由香飾演 IRUVA。
MAI NAMBU as MIWAKO, YURI ISHIHARA as Chaurus.
MAI NAMBU 飾演 MIWAKO，YURI ISHIHARA 飾演查魯斯。
JOUJI SHIBUE as TSUTOMU MURASHIGE, MOTOKI HANADA as Regrege.
澀江讓二飾演村重勉，花田元樹飾演雷古靈吉。
SHINYA YAMAMURA as TAKEO TANIGUCHI, RYOHEI SAKAI as Lucargol.
山村真哉飾演谷口武夫，酒井良平飾演盧卡盧果爾。
TOSHIKI KASHU as KAZAMATSURI.
嘉州俊樹飾演風祭。
RAURU is voiced by KENICHI SUZUMURA, and KOTA WADAZUMI plays RAURU.
RAURU 由 KENICHI SUZUMURA​​ 配音，KOTA WADAZUMI 飾演 RAURU。
MIKI NISHINO as NAOMI, RYOHEI SAKAI as Gaera.
西野美紀飾演直美，酒井良平飾演咖耶拉。
KOUHEI MATSUOKA as Zygarus.
松岡耕平飾演吉卡魯斯。
YUGO FUJII, IKUMI TANOUE, KOUHEI MATSUOKA as Golden Knight GARO SHO.
藤井佑吾、田上育美、松岡耕平飾演黄金騎士牙狼翔。
YUGO FUJII, KOUHEI MATSUOKA as Golden Knight GARO YAMI.
藤井佑吾、松岡耕平飾演黄金騎士牙狼伽羅。
YUGO FUJII plays the role of HAGANE.
藤井佑吾飾演①鋼鎧角色。
YUGO FUJII as KOUZAN knight ZANGO.
藤井佑吾飾演高山騎士藏吾。
YUUYA IWATAKI as SHIPPU, YUUYA BARANO as REPPU.
岩瀧悠哉飾演“SHIPPU”，原野悠也飾演“REPPU”。
SHO IKUSHIMA as KOUJI SUGITA, YUUKI HISADA as SHINTANI, FUSAKU TANI as HARANISHI.
生島翔飾演杉田浩二，久田佑樹飾演新谷，谷福作原西。
TAKAHIRO FUKUYA plays the role of homeless person, AYANO KATO, MIZUHO HIIRAGI, and MARINA ARISATO play the role of HORROR.
福谷貴宏飾演無家可歸者，加藤綾乃、柊瑞穗、有里麻里奈飾演駭魔角色。
MIYU MURASHIMA as MARIE, MIREI KAMIYAMA as MOMOKO, IKUMI and ASA as dancers, and TAKAHIRO SAKAI as staff.
MIYU MURASHIMA 飾演 MARIE，MIREI KAMIYAMA 飾演 MOMOKO，IKUMI 和 ASA 擔任舞者，TAKAHIRO SAKAI 擔任工作人員。
Original work by KEITA AMEMIYA.
雨宮惠太的原創作品。
Executive producer KIYOTAKA NINOMIYA.
執行製片二宮清隆。
Planning/producer Tanaka Aya, producer Higa Ichiro, SHUHEI OKABAYASHI.
企劃/製作人田中文、製作人比嘉一郎、岡林修平。
Photography by JUNYA HOSHI, AKIRA NISHIOKA.
攝影：JUNYA HOSHI、AKIRA NISHIOKA。
Stylist MASAHIKO KURODA, hair and makeup artists TSUGURU NASUNO, YU YAMAI.
造型師 MASAHIKO KURODA、髮型師和化妝師 TSUGURU NASUNO、YU YAMAI。
Assistant director JUNPEI SHIOKAWA, SHUHEI OKUMURA, assistant cinematographer KEI MARUYAMA, DAIKI KATO.
副導演鹽川淳平、奧村週平、助理攝影師丸山圭、加藤大樹。
Stylist assistants AYANO JOKO, YURIKA SUZUKI, SHIORI OMORI.
造型助理 AYANO JOKO、YURIKA SUZUKI、SHIORI OMORI。
Special photography YUI DOUTAN, CHIHARU KASAI, SHIORI KATSUMATA.
特別攝影 YUI DOUTAN、Chiharu Kasai、SHIORI KATSUMATA。
Stunt coordinator KAZUYOSHI SAKUMA, stunt actors YUGO FUJII, KOUHEI MATSUOKA, MOTOKI HANADA.
特技指導佐隈一義、特技演員藤井佑吾、松岡耕平、花田元樹。
Special cooperation SANSEI R&D.
特別合作SANSEI研發。
Produced by TOHOKUSHINSHA.
東北新社製作。
Screenplay NORIKATSU KODAMA, RIUJI YOSHIZAKI.
編劇：兒玉則勝、吉崎理二。
Screenplay cooperation: YASUHIRO MATSUDA, YUUWA TANAKA, YOSHIKATSU KIMURA.
劇本合作：松田泰弘、田中雄和、木村芳勝。
Stunt director MASAKI SUZUMURA.
特技導演鈴村正樹。
Director YASUHIRO MATSUDA, YUUWA TANAKA, YOSHIKATSU KIMURA.
導演松田康弘、田中悠和、木村勝利。
This is a fictional story.
這是一個虛構的故事。
This has nothing to do with any real people, organizations, or events.
這與任何真實的人、組織或事件無關。